https://www.thewinebuff.com/privacy-policy

My Account
Wish List (0)
0 item(s) - €0.00
Your shopping cart is empty!
+353 61 423904
INFO@THEWINEBUFF.COM
HOMEGifts2 Bottle Gifts6 Bottle GiftsWineLiqueurCreme de CassisRed WineAlfrocheiro PretoAlicanteBarberaBardolinoBobalBonardaCabernet FrancCanaioloCarignanColorinoCorvinaDolcettoGamayGrenacheJaenMalvasia NeraMarselanMencia JaenMerlotMolinaraMonastrell MourvedreMontepulcianoMourvedreNebbioloNegroamaroNero d'AvolaPetit VerdotPinotageRefosco dal Preduncolo RossoRondineliaSangioveseSyrah/ShirazTinto RorizTouriga FrancaCabernet SauvignonPrimitivoTouriga BarrocaTouriga NacionalTouriga RorizMalbecPinot NoirTempranilloWhite WineAlbariñoAligoteArintoArneisAzalBicalChenin BlancClairetteEncruzadoGarganegaGewurztraminerGodelloGrenacheGrüner VeltlinerLoureiroMacabeoMalvasia FinaMelon de BourgogneMuscadelleMuscatPiquepoulRieslingRoussanneSemillonTempranilloTrajaduraVerdejoVerdicchioViognierViuraChardonnayPinot GrigioSauvignon BlancRose WineCinsaultPinot GrigioCabernet FrancGrenacheMerlotSparkling WineAlicanteCarignanChardonnayCinsaultGrenacheMacabeoMerlotMonastrell MourvedreParelladaPinot AuxerroisPinot NoirRefoscoRieslingXarelloGleraChampagne WinePinot MeunierPinot NoirChardonnayFortified WinePortSherryDessert WineFurmintHárslevelüMuscadelleSauvignon BlancMuscatSemillonOur ShopsThe Wine Buff CorkThe Wine Buff Dungarvan The Wine Buff EnnisThe Wine Buff GalwayThe Wine Buff GlasthuleThe Wine Buff GoreyThe Wine Buff KilkennyThe Wine Buff LimerickThe Wine Buff NenaghThe Wine Buff PortarlingtonThe Wine Buff SligoThe Wine Buff St EmilionKinsale ConcessionLetterkenny ConcessionPortlaoise ConcessionBlogFranchisingAbout UsContact Us
Home
» Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Information
Click and Collect
Our Shops
Wine Delivery
About Us
your privacy
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. When you choose to order wine on our web site, you will be sked for  your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. These details will never be shared with a third party and will be held securely in our database. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
You will be asked to enter your card security number in order to further secure your shopping experience. We do not store your credit card details or make them available to you when you make another order through your account for your protection.
Please ensure that your account password is known only by you. If you believe someone else to have obtained your password, please contact us so that we can suspend your account.
ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY
The online privacy policy refers to information collecteed through or web site online and not to information collected offline.
cookies
We curently use cookies to gather information about your experience whilst here, to assist in the technology used to enable your account on the website and also to use the e-commerce features enabled on this website.
GOOGLE ANALYTICS
Our website uses Google Analytics (a web analytics service), which sets a cookie on your web browser in order to evaluate your experience of our website. The cookie is used to store information, such as what time you visited our website, whether you have visited the site before, what site referred you or what you searched for to find us.
INFORMED CONSENT
If you continue to browse our website without changing your cookie settings, we will presume that you are happy to receive this cookie from our website. If, however, you are not happy to receive cookies from our website, you can change your browser cookie settings at any time.
AVOIDING WEBSITE COOKIES
If you wish not to receive cookies from this website, you can change your web browser settings so that you will be notified when any website tries to send you a cookie. At this point you can choose to accept or refuse the cookie. In addition you can also delete historical cookies from your browser at any time.
In order to manage cookies please refer to your web browsers help function, which will guide you through the process of managing your browsers privacy settings. Alternatively, you may want to visit www.aboutcookies.org, an independent website which contains comprehensive information on how to do this on a wide variety of desktop browsers.
Alternatively if you wish just to avoid Google Analytic cookies consider Google’s browser plug-in available for most web browsers “Opt-out of Google Analytics cookies“.
why you need to know about COOKIES
A cookie is a simple text file that is stored on your website visitors computers when they land on your website. Cookies allow your website to record things such as; what search terms they entered into a search engine to find your website or how many people came to your website on a specific day. In other instances cookies are used to provide core functionality such as; keeping members logged in to your website or enabling customers to buy products or services from you via the website.
On the 26th May 2012 the New EU cookie law (e-Privacy Directive) came into effect which meant that any website using cookie technology must inform visitors that cookies were being used and what for.
CHANGES to policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
